[
  {
    "question": "Who was the best James Bond?",
    "answers": [
      "Sean Connery",
      "David Niven",
      "George Lazenby",
      "Roger Moore",
      "Timothy Dalton",
      "Pierce Brosnan",
      "Daniel Craig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best song by Toto?",
    "answers": ["Africa", "Hold the Line", "Rosanna", "Pamela"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your favorite pizza topping?",
    "answers": ["Pepperoni", "Canadian Bacon", "Pineapple", "BBQ Chicken"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the better captain?",
    "answers": ["Picard", "Kirk"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best defense?",
    "answers": ["A good offense", "A gooder defense"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which?",
    "answers": ["Alabama", "Auburn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of cheese is the moon made of?",
    "answers": ["Swiss", "Cheddar", "Provolone"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the best President of the United States?",
    "answers": [
      "Abraham Lincoln",
      "Theodore Roosevelt",
      "Franklin Roosevelt",
      "John F. Kennedy",
      "George Washington",
      "John Adams",
      "Thomas Jefferson",
      "Dwight D. Eisenhower",
      "Andrew Jackson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is your preferred hardware store?",
    "answers": ["Home Depot", "Lowes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much water do you drink per day?",
    "answers": [
      "None",
      "Less than a glass",
      "Between one and three glasses",
      "Between three and 7 glasses",
      "Eight or more glasses"
    ]
  }
]
